{
    "subject": "resource/Paora_Winitana",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Winitana, Paora",
    "human_readable": "The full name of Paora Winitana is Winitana, Paora.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9856674075126648,
            "question": "What is the full name of Paora Winitana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.955860435962677,
            "question": "Who is Paora Winitana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9047726988792419,
            "question": "Does the full name of Paora Winitana appear in any notable historical records or documents?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8247412443161011,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Paora and Winitana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8099030256271362,
            "question": "What is the cultural or ethnic background of Paora Winitana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7421734929084778,
            "question": "Has Paora Winitana won any notable awards or recognition?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.674372673034668,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Paora Winitana's early life or education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6449439525604248,
            "question": "Has Paora Winitana made any significant contributions to a particular field or discipline?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5963329076766968,
            "question": "Is Winitana a common surname in your knowledge graph?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44541501998901367,
            "question": "Is Paora a common given name in your knowledge graph?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The full name of Paora Winitana is Winitana, Paora.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Winitana a common surname in your knowledge graph?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Paora Winitana made any significant contributions to a particular field or discipline?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Paora Winitana's early life or education?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe correct format for Paora Winitana's full name is  \"Paora Te Puataata-a-tia Winitana\" as stated in several documents. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I will evaluate whether the triple statement is supported.\n\nThe triple statement is:\n\"The full name of Paora Winitana is Winitana, Paora.\"\n\nFrom the provided context information:\n\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4/re-ranker-msmarco/11.txt\n\t+ Personal\n\t\t- Full name is Paora Te Puataata-a-tia Winitana\n\nThe full name of Paora Winitana is indeed \"Paora Te Puataata-a-tia Winitana\", which is different from the triple statement.\n\nTherefore, the answer in JSON format is:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the provided documents, the full name given for Paora Winitana is \"Paora Te Puataata-a-tia Winitana,\" not just \"Winitana, Paora.\" Therefore, the statement that his full name is simply \"Winitana, Paora\" is incorrect."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The context states his full name is Paora Te Puataata-a-tia Winitana.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The full name of Paora Winitana provided in context 5 and context 3 as \"Paora Te Puataata-a-tia Winitana\" contradicts the statement, indicating that the first part (\"Winitana\") should actually be the last name.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The full name provided in the context information is Paora Te Puataata-a-tia Winitana.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}